Guide to the John Farquhar Fulton Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- General Files, 1910-1960; Series I
  - Hooper, Alice F. B., 1933-1945 (Box 84, Folder 1168-1169)
  - Horrax, Gilbert, 1928-1957 (Box 84, Folder 1170)
  - Horstmann, Dorothy M., 1944-1960 (Box 84, Folder 1171-1172)
  - Horton, Richard G., 1937-1944 (Box 84, Folder 1173)
  - Horwitz, Norman H., 1949-1954 (Box 84, Folder 1174)
  - Hoskins, R. G., 1933 (Box 84, Folder 1175)
  - Houssay, Bernardo A., 1935-1959 (Box 84, Folder 1176)
  - Howard, Marion E., 1944-1958 (Box 84, Folder 1177)
  - Howard-Jones, Norman, 1947-1948 (Box 84, Folder 1178)
  - Howe, Howard A., 1931-1941 (Box 84, Folder 1179)
  - Howe, Quincy, 1936-1941 (Box 85, Folder 1180)
  - Howell, William H., 1934-1935 (Box 85, Folder 1181)
    See also: box 223, folder 420
  - Hubbard, Oscar W., 1932 (Box 85, Folder 1182)
  - Hubbell, Florence Fulton
    - 1920-1922, 1930-1940 (Box 85, Folder 1183-1191)
    - 1941-1960 (Box 86, Folder 1192-1198)
  - Hubbell, Ralph
    - 1934-1941 April (Box 86, Folder 1199-1201)
    - 1941 May-1956 (Box 87, Folder 1202-1208)
  - Hughes, Robert A., 1948-1958 (Box 87, Folder 1209)
  - Hughson, Walter, 1935-1939 (Box 87, Folder 1210)
  - Hume, Edgar E., 1936-1945 (Box 87, Folder 1211)
  - Hume, Edward H., 1933-1954 (Box 87, Folder 1212)
  - Humm, Frances D., 1943 (Box 87, Folder 1213)
  - Hunneman, Eleanor, 1934-1959 (Box 87, Folder 1214)
  - Hunt, Rachel and Roy, 1941-1960 (Box 88, Folder 1215)
  - Hunter, Francis T., 1936-1940 (Box 88, Folder 1216)
  - Hunter, Richard and MacAlpine, Ida, 1956-1960 (Box 88, Folder 1217-1218)
  - Huntington Library, 1931-1942 (Box 88, Folder 1219)
  - Hurlbutt, Frank Jr, 1939 (Box 88, Folder 1220)
  - Hussey, Raymond, 1930-1937 (Box 88, Folder 1221)
  - Hyde, Jane E., 1944 (Box 88, Folder 1222)
  - Hydén, Holger, 1948-1958 (Box 88, Folder 1223)
  - Hyman, Chester, 1946-1960 (Box 88, Folder 1224)
  - Iba-Ing (Box 88, Folder 1225)
  - Inn-Iz (Box 88, Folder 1226)
  - Inay, Meliha, 1935-1959 (Box 88, Folder 1227)
  - Ingraham, Franc and Martha
    See also: box 180, folder 2677
    - 1928-1930 (Box 88, Folder 1228)
    - 1931-1960 (Box 89, Folder 1229-1232)
  - Institute for Advanced Study, 1942-1960 (Box 89, Folder 1233-1238)
    See also: box 69, folders 959-960
  - Institute for Living, 1943-1944 (Box 89, Folder 1239)
  - Institute of Ophthalmology, 1944-1945 (Box 89, Folder 1240)
  - Institute of the Aeronautical Sciences, 1941-1942 (Box 90, Folder 1241-1243)
  - International College of Surgeons, 1952-1957 (Box 90, Folder 1244)
  - International Congress for the History of Science, 1952-1953, 1959 (Box 90, Folder 1245)
  - International Congress of Neurological Sciences, 1957 (Box 90, Folder 1246)
  - International Congress of Neurology, 1938-1939, 1949, 1956 (Box 90, Folder 1247-1248)
  - International Congress of Psychology, 1929, 1932 (Box 90, Folder 1249)
  - International Congress of the History of Medicine, 1927-1958 (Box 90, Folder 1250-1251)
  - International Physiological Congress, 1926-1956 (Box 90, Folder 1252)
  - Internationale Medizinische Woche, 1936 (Box 90, Folder 1253)
  - Interne Council of America, 1938-1940 (Box 90, Folder 1254)
  - Irving, James T., 1938-1952 (Box 91, Folder 1255)
  - Irwin, George R., 1944 (Box 91, Folder 1256)
  - Isis
    See: boxes 81-82, folders 1137-1145
  - Ivy, Andrew C., 1932-1951 (Box 91, Folder 1257-1258)
  - Izquierdo, J. Joaquin, 1934-1960 (Box 91, Folder 1259)
  - Ja (Box 91, Folder 1260)
  - Je (Box 91, Folder 1261)
  - Jo-Jonc (Box 91, Folder 1262)
  - Jone-Ju (Box 91, Folder 1263)
  - J. B. Lippincott Company, 1929-1946 (Box 91, Folder 1264)
  - Jackson, William A., 1937-1959 (Box 91, Folder 1265)
  - Jacobs, Henry Barton, 1925-1936 (Box 91, Folder 1266)
  - Jacobsen, Carlyle F., 1932-1955 (Box 92, Folder 1267-1268)
  - James, J. E., 1925-1932 (Box 92, Folder 1269)
  - Jarvis, D. C., 1939 (Box 92, Folder 1270)
  - Jasper, Herbert, 1936-1959 (Box 92, Folder 1271)
  - Jefferson, Geoffrey, 1926-1960 (Box 92, Folder 1272)
  - John Carter Brown Library, 1932-1959 (Box 92, Folder 1273)
  - Johns Hopkins Medical Society, 1940-1941 (Box 92, Folder 1274)
  - Johns Hopkins University: Friends of the Library, 1933-1936 (Box 92, Folder 1275)
  - Johnson, Allen S., 1934-1949 (Box 92, Folder 1276)
  - Johnson, John, 1928-1953 (Box 92, Folder 1277-1278)
    See also: boxes 137-138, folders 1858-1877
  - Johnson, Robert E., 1935 (Box 92, Folder 1279)
  - Jokl, Ernst, 1941-1944 (Box 92, Folder 1280)
  - Jones, Benjamin F., 1926-1942 (Box 92, Folder 1281)
  - Jones, F. Wood, 1929-1936; 1953 (Box 93, Folder 1282)
  - Jones, Hardin B., 1944 (Box 93, Folder 1283)
  - Jones, Harold W., 1937-1949 (Box 93, Folder 1284)
  - Jones, Richard F., 1931-1937 (Box 93, Folder 1285)
  - Josiah Macy, Jr. Foundation, 1952-1955 (Box 93, Folder 1286)
  - Joslin, Elliott P., 1923, 1933-1950 (Box 93, Folder 1287)
  - Journal de Physiologie, 1932-1954 (Box 93, Folder 1288)
  - Journal of Anatomy, 1934-1937 (Box 93, Folder 1289)
  - Journal of Applied Physiology, 1948 (Box 93, Folder 1290)
  - Journal of Aviation Medicine, 1940-1942 (Box 93, Folder 1291)
  - Journal of Clinical Investigation, 1945-1947 (Box 93, Folder 1292)
  - Journal of General Physiology, 1930 (Box 93, Folder 1293)
  - Journal of Human Physiology, 1930-1931 (Box 93, Folder 1294)
  - Journal of Nervous and Mental Disease, 1925-1945 (Box 93, Folder 1295)
  - Journal of Neurosurgery, 1943-1946, 1959 (Box 93, Folder 1296)
    See also: box 48, Folder 714
  - Journal of Nutrition, 1931-1932 (Box 93, Folder 1297)
  - Journal of Pharmacology and ExperimentalTheraputics, 1930-1931 (Box 93, Folder 1298)
  - Journal of Physiology, 1927-1935 (Box 93, Folder 1299)
  - Journal of the American Medical Association, 1927-1955 (Box 93, Folder 1300-1301)
    See also: boxes 51-52, folders 760-764
  - Journal of the Canadian Association of Medical Students and Interns, 1944 (Box 93, Folder 1302)
  - Joy, Robert J. T., 1954-1960 (Box 93, Folder 1303)
  - Judd, Albert, 1938 (Box 93, Folder 1304)
  - Judson, Barbara, 1939-1950 (Box 94, Folder 1305)
  - Judson, Patricia, 1943-1959 (Box 94, Folder 1306)
  - Judson, Paul K., 1920-1944 (Box 94, Folder 1307)
  - Ka (Box 94, Folder 1308)
  - Ke-Kel (Box 94, Folder 1309)
  - Kem-Kez (Box 94, Folder 1310)
  - Kh-Kn (Box 94, Folder 1311)
  - Ko-Ky (Box 94, Folder 1312)
  - Kaada, Birger Rygg, 1947-1960 (Box 94, Folder 1313)
  - Kaempffert, Waldemar, 1940-1942 (Box 94, Folder 1314)
  - Kahn, Edgar A., 1933-1946 (Box 94, Folder 1315)
  - Kahn, Eugen, 1930-1941 (Box 95, Folder 1316)
  - Kaplan, Abraham, 1930-1959 (Box 95, Folder 1317)
  - Kaplan, Sylvan J., 1949-1958 (Box 95, Folder 1318)
  - Kasdon, S. Charles, 1933-1958 (Box 95, Folder 1319)
  - Kato, Genichi, 1934-1955 (Box 95, Folder 1320)
  - Katsuki, Yasuji, 1952-1959 (Box 95, Folder 1321)
  - Katz, Louis N., 1925-1944 (Box 95, Folder 1322)
  - Kaufman, Samuel S., 1945-1947 (Box 95, Folder 1323)
  - Kaufman; William, 1940-1959 (Box 95, Folder 1324)
  - Kebat, Herman, 1935 (Box 95, Folder 1325)
  - Keefe, Grace, 1948-1949 (Box 95, Folder 1326)
  - Keefer, Chester, 1944 (Box 95, Folder 1327)
  - Keele, Kenneth, 1951-1960 (Box 95, Folder 1328)
  - Keen, Florence, 1944-1946 (Box 95, Folder 1329)
  - Keevil, John J., 1949-1953 (Box 95, Folder 1330)
  - Kekwick, Alan, 1952-1959 (Box 95, Folder 1331)
  - Kellaway, Charles, 1941-1944 (Box 95, Folder 1332)
  - Keller, Allen D.
    - 1926-1932 (Box 95, Folder 1333-1334)
    - 1933-1958 (Box 96, Folder 1335-1337)
  - Keller, Deane, 1939-1960 (Box 96, Folder 1338-1339)
  - Keller, Marion, 1931-1934 (Box 96, Folder 1340)
  - Kellog, Kenneth E., 1939-1940 (Box 96, Folder 1341)
  - Kelly, Gerald, 1956-1958 (Box 96, Folder 1342)
  - Kelly, J. Frederick, 1929 (Box 96, Folder 1343)
  - Kennard, Margaret (Box 96, Folder 1344-1345)
    - 1931-1934 (Box 96, Folder 1344-1345)
    - 1935-1960 (Box 97, Folder 1346-1352)
  - Kennedy, Foster, 1933-1942, 1950 (Box 97, Folder 1353)
  - Kent, R. H., 1943-1945 (Box 98, Folder 1354)
  - Kenyon, Marjorie S., 1936-1953 (Box 98, Folder 1355-1356)
  - Kenyon College, 1938-1959 (Box 98, Folder 1357)
    General
    See also: box 30, folders 427-428
  - Kerby, Leslie R. V., 1930-1959 (Box 98, Folder 1358)
  - Kessler, Morris, 1938-1959 (Box 98, Folder 1359)
  - Kessler, Stanley, 1950 (Box 98, Folder 1360)
  - Keynes, Geoffrey
    - 1928-1947 (Box 98, Folder 1361-1365)
    - 1948-1960 (Box 99, Folder 1366-1369)
  - Keynes, Quentin, 1939-1959 (Box 99, Folder 1370-1371)
  - Keynes, Richard, 1947-1959 (Box 99, Folder 1372)
  - Keys, Thomas E., 1939-1960 (Box 99, Folder 1373)
  - Kilgour, Frederick G., 1951-1960 (Box 99, Folder 1374)
  - Killick, Horace, Evelyn, amd Wendy, 1940-1943 (Box 99, Folder 1375)
  - Kim, Chul, 1954-1960 (Box 99, Folder 1376)
  - King, Raphael, 1936,1952 (Box 99, Folder 1377)
  - Kisch, Bruno, 1938-1960 (Box 99, Folder 1378-1379)
  - Klebs, Arnold C.
    - 1927-1935 March (Box 100, Folder 1380-1389)
    - 1935 April-1938 April (Box 101, Folder 1390-1398)
    - 1938 May-1943 (Box 102, Folder 1399-1410)
  - Klemme, Roland M., 1933-1946 (Box 103, Folder 1411)
  - Klemperer, Wolfgang, 1944-1960 (Box 103, Folder 1412)
  - Klickstein, Herbert S., 1950-1958 (Box 103, Folder 1413)
  - Klüver, Heinrich, 1932-1960 (Box 103, Folder 1414)
  - Knollenberg, Bernhard, 1938-1945 (Box 103, Folder 1415)
  - Knopf, Alfred A., 1943-1960 (Box 103, Folder 1416)
  - Knowlton, Mildred, 1949 (Box 103, Folder 1417)
  - Kock, Wolfram, 1954-1960 (Box 103, Folder 1418)
  - Köbcke, Heinz, 1938-1954 (Box 103, Folder 1419)
  - Koskoff, Yale, 1930-1959 (Box 103, Folder 1420)
  - Krieg, Wendell, 1944-1954 (Box 103, Folder 1421)
  - Kronhaus, Edgardo, 1933-1934 (Box 103, Folder 1421A)
  - Kruger, Lawrence, 1949-1959 (Box 103, Folder 1421B)
  - Krumbhaar, Edward B., 1927-1954 (Box 103, Folder 1422-1423)
    See also: Series II, boxes 240-246, folders 706-766
  - Kruta, Vladislav, 1955-1960 (Box 104, Folder 1424)
  - Kubie, Lawrence S., 1927-1958 (Box 104, Folder 1425)
  - Kuffler, Stephen, 1943-1958 (Box 104, Folder 1426)
  - La-Lap (Box 104, Folder 1427)
  - Lar-Laz (Box 104, Folder 1428)
  - Le-Lel (Box 104, Folder 1429)
  - Len-Ley (Box 104, Folder 1430)
  - Lh-Ll (Box 104, Folder 1431)
  - Lo (Box 104, Folder 1432)
  - Lu-Ly (Box 105, Folder 1433)
  - Lackland, E. C., 1935-1939 (Box 105, Folder 1434)
  - LaFia, David J., 1947-1960 (Box 105, Folder 1435)
  - Lamport, Harold, 1942-1960 (Box 105, Folder 1436-1438)
    See also: Series II, box 223, folder 421
  - Lancet, 1929-1957 (Box 105, Folder 1439)
  - Landis, Eugene M., 1929-1953 (Box 105, Folder 1440-1443)
  - Lang, Edward, 1949 (Box 105, Folder 1444)
  - Langford, Clara Wheaton, 1921-1924 (Box 105, Folder 1445)
  - Langley, Leroy
    - 1940-1943 (Box 105, Folder 1446)
    - 1944-1959 (Box 106, Folder 1447)
  - Langstroth, Lovell, 1954-1955 (Box 106, Folder 1448)
  - Langworthy, Orthello, 1927-1941 (Box 106, Folder 1449)
  - Lapicque, Louis, 1926-1947 (Box 106, Folder 1450)
  - Larkey, Sanford, 1932-1959 (Box 106, Folder 1451-1452)
  - Larron, Gunvor, 1952-1959 (Box 106, Folder 1453)
  - Larsell, Olof, 1934-1959 (Box 106, Folder 1454)
  - Lashley, Karl S., 1932-1951 (Box 106, Folder 1455)
  - Laugier, Henri, 1923, 1941 (Box 106, Folder 1456)
  - Laurens, Henry, 1935-1936 (Box 106, Folder 1457)
  - Lawrence, Ernest O., 1958-1959 (Box 106, Folder 1458)
  - Lawrence, John H.
    - 1938-1944 August (Box 106, Folder 1459-1460)
    - 1944 September-1960 (Box 107, Folder 1461-1462)
  - Lea & Febiger, 1926-1934 (Box 107, Folder 1463)
  - Leake, Chauncey
    - 1928-1949 (Box 107, Folder 1464-1469)
    - 1950-1960 (Box 108, Folder 1470-1472)
  - Learmonth, James R., 1929-1952 (Box 108, Folder 1473)
  - Lebedenko, V., 1944-1945 (Box 108, Folder 1474)
  - Lee, Douglas, 1946-1949 (Box 108, Folder 1475)
  - LeFanu, William, 1935-1959 (Box 108, Folder 1476)
  - Lehman, Harvey C., 1937-1958 (Box 108, Folder 1477)
  - Lehmann, Walter M., 1929-1944 (Box 108, Folder 1478)
  - Lehoczky, Tibor, 1953-1958 (Box 108, Folder 1479)
  - Leibowitz, Joshua O., 1954-1960 (Box 108, Folder 1480)
  - Leikind, Morris C., 1936-1955 (Box 108, Folder 1481)
  - Leister, Herbert, 1946 (Box 108, Folder 1482)
  - Lennox, Margaret A., 1946-1954 (Box 108, Folder 1483)
  - Lennox, William G., 1939-1960 (Box 108, Folder 1484)
  - Lethin, Anton, 1950, 1954 (Box 108, Folder 1485)
  - Levin, Max, 1927-1928, 1938-1956 (Box 109, Folder 1486)
  - Levin, Paul M., 1938-1943 (Box 109, Folder 1487)
  - Levine, Herbert, 1950, 1951, 1957 (Box 109, Folder 1488)
  - Levine, Samuel A., 1930-1958 (Box 109, Folder 1489)
  - Lewis, C. R., 1941-1949 (Box 109, Folder 1490)
  - Lewis, Frederick T., 1940-1942 (Box 109, Folder 1491)
  - Lewis, G. Eric, 1929 (Box 109, Folder 1492)
  - Lewis, George Chase, 1939 (Box 109, Folder 1493)
  - Lewis, J. K., 1942-1943 (Box 109, Folder 1494)
  - Lewis, Roger A., 1952-1956 (Box 109, Folder 1495)
  - Lewis, Thomas, 1929-1938 (Box 109, Folder 1496)
  - Lewis, Wilmarth S., 1932-1959 (Box 109, Folder 1497-1498)
    See also: Series II, box 206, folder 151
  - Ley Gracia, Adolfo, 1934-1950 (Box 109, Folder 1499)
  - Libman, Emanuel, 1939-1942 (Box 109, Folder 1500)
  - Librarium, 1959-1961 (Box 109, Folder 1501)
  - Licht, Sidney, 1952-1959 (Box 109, Folder 1502)
  - Liddell, Edward G. T., 1924-1960 (Box 109, Folder 1503-1506)
  - Liddell, Howard S., 1930-1960 (Box 109, Folder 1507)
  - Liebert, Herman W., 1948-1960 (Box 109, Folder 1508)
  - Light, Richard U., 1931-1958 (Box 110, Folder 1509-1510)
  - Liljencrantz, Eric, 1941-1943 (Box 110, Folder 1511)
  - Liljestrand, Göran, 1926-1956 (Box 110, Folder 1512)
  - Lilly, John C., 1950-1960 (Box 110, Folder 1513)
  - Lim, Robert, 1931-1944 (Box 110, Folder 1514)
  - Lindau, Arvid, 1928-1956 (Box 110, Folder 1514)
  - Lindberg, Alexander, 1936-1959 (Box 110, Folder 1516)
  - Lindsley, Donald B., 1933-1960 (Box 110, Folder 1517)
  - Lippard, Margaret C., 1931-1936 (Box 110, Folder 1518)
  - Lippard, Vernon W., 1939, 1951-1952, 1958 (Box 110, Folder 1519)
  - Little, Brown and Co. (Box 110, Folder 1520)
    See also: box 10, folder 147
  - Liu, Helen and Wu-Chi, 1947-1955 (Box 110, Folder 1521)
  - Livingston, Robert B.
    See also: Series II, Box 223, Folder 423
    - 1946-1949 (Box 110, Folder 1522-1523)
    - 1950-1960 (Box 111, Folder 1524-1527)
  - Livingston, William K., 1932-1954 (Box 111, Folder 1528-1530)
  - Lloyd, David P. C., 1942-1958 (Box 112, Folder 1531)
    See also: Series II, Box 223, Folder 424
  - Lloyd-Luke Ltd., 1952-1960 (Box 112, Folder 1532)
  - Lockwood, John S., 1944-1954 (Box 112, Folder 1533)
  - Loeb, Robert F., 1935-1955 (Box 112, Folder 1534)
  - Loewi, Otto, 1937-1954 (Box 112, Folder 1535)
  - Long, C. N. Hugh, 1936-1959 (Box 112, Folder 1536)
  - Long, Esmond R., 1939-1960 (Box 112, Folder 1537)
  - Long, Perrin H., 1931-1955 (Box 112, Folder 1538)
  - Longmans, Green and Co., 1935 (Box 112, Folder 1539)
  - Lopašić, Radoslav, 1952-1956 (Box 112, Folder 1540)
    See also: box 9, folder 133
  - Lorente de Nó, Rafael, 1932-1958 (Box 112, Folder 1541-1545)
    See also: Series II, boxes 226-231, folders 467-531
  - Lorenz, Anthony J., 1955-1956 (Box 113, Folder 1546)
  - Lotz, Myron M., 1954-1958 (Box 113, Folder 1547)
  - Love, Albert, 1940-1944, 1960 (Box 113, Folder 1548)
  - Love, Jack W., 1952-1958 (Box 113, Folder 1549)
  - Lovelace, W. Randolph, 1942-1946 (Box 113, Folder 1550)
  - Lovett, Sidney, 1945-1958 (Box 113, Folder 1551)
  - Lowenstein, Bertrand, 1945-1958 (Box 113, Folder 1552)
  - Lowery, Marklove, 1946-1953 (Box 113, Folder 1553)
  - Luck, J. Murray, 1940-1946 (Box 113, Folder 1554)
  - Luckhardt, Arno B., 1929-1951 (Box 113, Folder 1555)
  - Lull, George F., 1946-1947 (Box 113, Folder 1556)
  - Lundbaek, Knud, 1947-1960 (Box 113, Folder 1557)
  - Lydenberg, H. M., 1936-1955 (Box 113, Folder 1558)
  - Lyerly, James G., 1939-1940 (Box 113, Folder 1559)
  - Lyons, Richard, 1954 (Box 113, Folder 1560)
  - Ma-Macc (Box 114, Folder 1561)
  - Macd-Maci (Box 114, Folder 1562)
  - Mack (Box 114, Folder 1563)
  - Macl-Macm (Box 114, Folder 1564)
  - Macn-Macy (Box 114, Folder 1565)
  - Mad-Maj (Box 114, Folder 1566)
  - Mak-Map (Box 114, Folder 1567)
  - Mar-Mas (Box 114, Folder 1568)
  - Mat-Maz (Box 114, Folder 1569)
  - MD-Med (Box 114, Folder 1570)
  - Mee-Men (Box 115, Folder 1571)
  - Mer-Meu (Box 115, Folder 1572)
  - Mic-Mil (Box 115, Folder 1573)
  - Min-Mix (Box 115, Folder 1574)
  - Mod-Moo (Box 115, Folder 1575)
  - Mor-Moy (Box 115, Folder 1576)
  - Mu-My (Box 115, Folder 1577)
  - M. Lehmann, Inc., 1936-1940 (Box 115, Folder 1578)
  - MacKay, E., 1942-1944 (Box 115, Folder 1579)
  - MacKeith, Malcolm, 1926-1935 (Box 115, Folder 1580)
  - Macken, Daniel, 1956-1960 (Box 116, Folder 1581)
  - MacKevett, Edith, 1946-1956 (Box 116, Folder 1582)
  - MacKevett, Edward M., 1953-1956 (Box 116, Folder 1583)
  - MacKinney, Loren C., 1952-1960 (Box 116, Folder 1584)
  - Mackintosh, James M., 1942-1960 (Box 116, Folder 1585)
  - MacLean, Kenneth, 1932-1957 (Box 116, Folder 1586)
  - MacLean, Paul, 1945-1972 (Box 116, Folder 1587-1588)
  - MacLeish, Archibald, 1940-1942 (Box 116, Folder 1589)
  - MacMillan Co.
    - 1927-1932 (Box 116, Folder 1590)
    - 1933-1960 (Box 117, Folder 1591)
  - MacNalty, Sir Arthur, 1939-1960 (Box 117, Folder 1592)
  - MacPike, Eugene F., 1928-1962 (Box 117, Folder 1593-1594)
  - Maddison, R. E. W., 1954-1962 (Box 117, Folder 1595)
  - Magdalen College
    See also: box 136, folders 1856-1857
    - General, 1922-1953 (Box 117, Folder 1596)
    - Boase portrait, 1951-1954 (Box 117, Folder 1597-1598)
    - Boase Portrait Fund, 1949-1959 (Box 117, Folder 1599)
  - Magee, James, 1944 (Box 117, Folder 1600)
  - Magnus, Herdis von, 1946-1960 (Box 117, Folder 1601)
  - Magnus, Otto, 1941-1954 (Box 117, Folder 1602)
  - Magnus-Levy, Adolph, 1940-1950 (Box 118, Folder 1603-1605)
  - Magoun, Horace W., 1946-1958 (Box 118, Folder 1606)
  - Mahoney, William G., 1933-1959 (Box 118, Folder 1607-1608)
  - Major, Ralph H., 1938-1959 (Box 118, Folder 1609)
  - Malis, Leonard, 1950-1951 (Box 118, Folder 1610)
  - Maloeuf, Noble Samuel Royston (Box 119, Folder 1615)
  - Malloch, Archibald, 1922-1954 (Box 118, Folder 1611-1613)
  - Malmo, Robert, 1944-1955 (Box 119, Folder 1614)
  - Maluf, N. S. Rustum, 1938-1959 (Box 119, Folder 1615)
  - Mann, Agnes, 1922-1931 (Box 119, Folder 1616)
  - Mansell, Harold S., 1925-1940 (Box 119, Folder 1617)
  - Marchand, John, 1945-1954 (Box 119, Folder 1618)
  - Marchesi, Vincent, 1958-1960 (Box 119, Folder 1619)
  - Marchi, Paola, 1955-1956 (Box 119, Folder 1620)
  - Marco, Mildred, 1944-1948 (Box 119, Folder 1621)
  - Margaria, Rudolfo, 1948-1956 (Box 119, Folder 1622)
  - Mark, Edward L.
    See also: box 18, folder 262
    - 1920-1941 (Box 119, Folder 1623-1624)
    - 85th birthday celebration, 1932 (Box 119, Folder 1625)
  - Marmorston, Jessie, 1941-1955 (Box 119, Folder 1626)
  - Marquis, Donald, 1932-1950 (Box 119, Folder 1627)
  - Marshall, E. Kenneth, 1930-1941 (Box 120, Folder 1628)
  - Marshall, Jack, 1952-1958 (Box 120, Folder 1629)
  - Marshall, Mary Louise, 1945-1947 (Box 120, Folder 1630)
  - Marshall, Wade H., 1944-1958 (Box 120, Folder 1631)
  - Márti Ibáñez, Felix, 1953-1960 (Box 120, Folder 1632)
  - Martin, D. C., 1951 (Box 120, Folder 1633)
  - Martin, J. Purdon, 1928-1959 (Box 120, Folder 1634)
  - Martinez-Niochet, Arminio, 1946-1959 (Box 120, Folder 1635)
  - Maryland Psychiatric Society, 1941 (Box 120, Folder 1636)
  - Massachusetts Medical Society, 1941 (Box 120, Folder 1637)
  - Massier-Doucet, Yvonne, 1949-1960 (Box 120, Folder 1638-1639)
  - Masson et Cie, 1953-1959 (Box 120, Folder 1640)
  - Masur, Jack, 1950-1960 (Box 120, Folder 1641)
  - Matheson, A. Tom, 1949-1958 (Box 120, Folder 1642)
  - Matthews, Bryan, 1931-1945 (Box 120, Folder 1643)
  - May, Mark A., 1932-1934 (Box 120, Folder 1644)
  - Mayer, Claudius, 1946-1954 (Box 120, Folder 1645)
  - Mayer, Jean, 1951-1960 (Box 120, Folder 1646)
  - McAfee, Janet, 1935-1938 (Box 121, Folder 1647)
  - McCord, David, 1941-1958 (Box 121, Folder 1648)
  - McCouch, Grayson, 1926-1958 (Box 121, Folder 1649-1650)
  - McCullough, Warren, 1933-1956 (Box 121, Folder 1651)
  - McDaniel, William B., 1934-1956 (Box 121, Folder 1652)
  - McDonough, Stephen, 1940-1946 (Box 121, Folder 1653)
  - McDowell, R. J. S., 1930-1958 (Box 121, Folder 1654)
  - McFarland, Ross A., 1938-1957 (Box 121, Folder 1655)
  - McGavron, Joyce, 1931-1944 (Box 121, Folder 1656)
  - McGraw, Arthur B., 1934-1943 (Box 121, Folder 1657)
  - McGraw-Hill Co., 1945-1958 (Box 121, Folder 1658)
  - McHenry, Lawrence, 1954-1960 (Box 121, Folder 1659)
  - McIntire, Ross T., 1941-1942 (Box 121, Folder 1660)
  - McKenzie, Kenneth J., 1932-1960 (Box 121, Folder 1661)
  - McKie, Douglas, 1934-1960 (Box 121, Folder 1662)
  - McKie, William N., 1944-1953 (Box 122, Folder 1663)
  - McMenemy, William H., 1949-1956 (Box 122, Folder 1664)
  - Meagher, Richard, 1929-1936 (Box 122, Folder 1665-1666)
  - Medical and Surgical Supply Committee, 1940-1942 (Box 122, Folder 1667)
  - Medical Library Association
    See also: box 23, folder 328
    - 1940-1946 (Box 122, Folder 1668-1673)
    - 1947-1955 (Box 123, Folder 1674-1676)
  - Medical Research Council, 1929-1930, 1940-1942 (Box 123, Folder 1677-1678)
  - Medical Society of the County of Monroe, 1946 (Box 123, Folder 1679)
  - Medicine, 1929-1947 (Box 123, Folder 1680)
  - Meiklejohn, Andrew Peter, 1938-1941, 1958 (Box 123, Folder 1681)
  - Meldrum, Andrew N., 1932-1934 (Box 123, Folder 1682)
  - Mellanby, Edward and May, 1941-1958 (Box 123, Folder 1683)
  - Mellanby, John, 1928-1935 (Box 123, Folder 1684)
  - Mendel, Lafayette, 1929-1934 (Box 123, Folder 1685)
  - Mendell, Clarence, 1930-1935, 1953 (Box 123, Folder 1686)
  - Mendes Alves, Miguel, 1948-1958 (Box 123, Folder 1687)
  - Mendoza, Felipe, 1946-1949 (Box 123, Folder 1688)
  - Meriden Gravure Co., 1937 (Box 123, Folder 1689)
  - Merlis, Jerome, 1940-1953 (Box 123, Folder 1690)
  - Merritt, H. Houston, 1937-1955 (Box 123, Folder 1691)
  - Messimy, Robert, 1936-1952 (Box 123, Folder 1692)
  - Metcalf, Keyes D., 1945-1947 (Box 123, Folder 1693)
  - Mettier, Fred and Cecilia, 1932-1952 (Box 124, Folder 1694)
  - Meyer, Arthur W., 1933-1956 (Box 124, Folder 1695)
  - Meyer, Edith, 1941-1959 (Box 124, Folder 1696-1697)
  - Michaud, Jeanne, 1945-1949 (Box 124, Folder 1698)
  - Michel, Frances, 1933-1940 (Box 124, Folder 1699)
  - Mihaulović, Ljubodrag, 1953-1960 (Box 124, Folder 1700)
  - Miles, Walter, 1928-1959 (Box 124, Folder 1701-1702)
  - Miller, Frederick, 1926-1958 (Box 124, Folder 1703)
  - Miller, Genevieve, 1940-1960 (Box 124, Folder 1704-1705)
  - Miller, Hyman, 1942-1947 (Box 125, Folder 1706)
  - Miller, William S., 1936-1939 (Box 125, Folder 1707)
  - Millikan, Glenn, 1935-1947 (Box 125, Folder 1708)
  - Milroy, T. H., 1929 (Box 125, Folder 1709)
  - Minnesota Historical Society, 1930-1960 (Box 125, Folder 1710)
  - Mishkin, Mortimer, 1949-1950, 1960 (Box 125, Folder 1711)
  - Mitchell, George, 1949-1958 (Box 125, Folder 1712)
  - Modern Language Association of America, 1953 (Box 125, Folder 1713)
  - Moe, Henry Allen, 1933-1958 (Box 125, Folder 1714)
  - Monnier, Alexandre, 1929-1960 (Box 125, Folder 1715)
  - Monnier, Marcel, 1939-1949 (Box 125, Folder 1716)
  - Monrad-Krohn, George H., 1939-1952 (Box 125, Folder 1717)
  - Montagu, M. F. Ashley, 1935-1955 (Box 125, Folder 1718-1719)
  - Montgomery, Margot, 1936-1945 (Box 125, Folder 1720)
  - Montreal Neurological Institute (Box 125, Folder 1721)
    See also: box 136, folder 1847
  - Moore, Burness, 1946-1949 (Box 125, Folder 1722)
  - Moore, Francis, 1948-1956 (Box 125, Folder 1723)
  - Moore, James, 1930 (Box 125, Folder 1724)
  - Moore, Merrill, 1937-1951 (Box 125, Folder 1725)
  - Morelle, Jean, 1930-1959 (Box 125, Folder 1726)